[{"answer": "I want to feel like I broke into the studio and took over and made them mad.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 10, "question": "What on earth will Bill Maher say tonight?", "qSentId": 9}, {"answer": "No probably about it.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "It's not in their interest to do a deal, is it?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "Well, I like this quote from Warren Buffett who says the way to get rid of the deficit, we should pass a law that says any time there's a deficit of more than 3 percent of GDP, all sitting members of Congress are ineligible for reelection.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "Isn't it the Congress' job to present a jobs bill?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "Well, if you're talking about social mobility, yes.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "So it's all surprising to me that the people governing the country pander to that by this rhetoric of everything has to make a profit because that's the way you have a yardstick of success here, isn't it?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "Because it shows we're falling behind China.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "Why is it scary?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "But we would have to reconfigure all of our priorities.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "Can America afford to see everything economically, militarily and so on as a threat in the way it has before?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "See, many Americans, it seems to me -- I mean you say this stuff and I bet you get deluged with people calling you unpatriotic, un-American.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "Who's the threat that's going to invade us?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "What's patriotic is wanting your country to succeed.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "But, I mean, is it time that America completely changed its philosophy on these things?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "None.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "How many do the Chinese have?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "A hundred and 25,000 millionaires in Shanghai.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "How many?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "I would need a gun to my head.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "Palin or Bachmann?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "Is it possible in the current climate?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "That's a great question.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "Is America more or less racist now since Obama has been in power?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "Well, you know, hopefully Mitt Romney.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "Are there other any of the Republican candidates so far that have emerged that you would see as potentially not life threatening?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "Jimmy Carter was an amazingly principled president.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "Has there ever been a president in your lifetime who has been properly principled in your eyes?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "Well, not that, is there's a kind of expectation from this mass populace that you have to do certain things.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "It attracts criticism?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "You know I love him.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "How do you think Obama is doing as president?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "Is it, though?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "If a Democrat gets in and we don't attempt Democratic policy.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "What should he be doing right now?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "I think I'm just practical.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "But what tag are you proudest of putting yourself to?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "You hate their ideology, don't you think?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "But do you -- I mean you're a Democrat?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "I mean I'm certainly more in line with their thinking.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "How would you describe yourself?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "Do you vote?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "Almost always.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "Democrat?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "Ever voted Republican?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "I voted for McCain in the 2000 primary.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "When?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "First of all, there is no such thing as a sexaholic.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Have you aborted on being a sexaholic?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "This always comes up.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "Are you still attending the Playboy mansion on a regular basis?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "I have.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "Doesn't that say something for me?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "I went in the grotto.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "You went in the grotto?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "You are beginning to sound a bit defensive about this, Bill.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "Why don't they get on his case?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "This job?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "Is part of the trick of show business knowing when to leave the party?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "Gee, what a question that is.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "What do you make of him as a human being?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "Stress.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 641, "question": "What is the secret of your age-defying presence today?", "qSentId": 640}, {"answer": "Well, it's all I've ever really wanted to do.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 651, "question": "What's your motivation to keep working now?", "qSentId": 650}, {"answer": "I think the best movie I made was \"Glory\".", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 675, "question": "What would be your personal favorite?", "qSentId": 674}, {"answer": "Oh, heaven now you've got a long list.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 685, "question": "Who have been the greatest male and female actors of your lifetime?", "qSentId": 684}, {"answer": "I mean, the most fun.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 698, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 697}, {"answer": "That's for me to know and you to find out.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 701, "question": "What did you and Clint get up to that we don't know about?", "qSentId": 700}, {"answer": "Well, it's interesting.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 708, "question": "What do you make of the modern Hollywood scene?", "qSentId": 707}, {"answer": "Act.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 714, "question": "What would be the best piece of advice you would give to an up and coming actor?", "qSentId": 713}, {"answer": "Doesn't matter where you go to work.", "docId": "110715pmt", "aSentId": 717, "question": "Simple as that?", "qSentId": 716}]